const questionBank = [
    {
      question: 'Question 1: Why do dogs eat grass?',
      answers: [
        'The property that causes humans to itch actually helps dogs digest food',
        'It makes them look tougher, more daring, and thus more attractive to mates',
        'They can develop a craving for micronutrients found only in grass',
        'To help purge intestinal parasites'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'To help purge intestinal parasites',
    },
    {
      question: 'Question 2: Why do cats like boxes?',
      answers: [
        'They instinctually know that boxes hold goods and they like to think of themselves as \'good\'',
        'Boxes help to insulate temperature',
        'Boxes are appealing environments to ambush predators',
        'Since boxes have 8 sides, and cats have 9 lives, they naturally trust boxes more than other containers'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Boxes are appealing environments to ambush predators',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why do birds poop everywhere?',
      answers: [
        'They lack colons and bladders so they cannot store waste',
        'They like to ruin people\'s days',
        'They strategically relieve themselves to escape predators',
        'They use droppings to mark their territory'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'They lack colons and bladders so they cannot store waste',
    },
    {
      question: 'Do rodents hibernate?',
      answers: [
        'Yes, they all do!',
        'No, none of them do!',
        'No, only larger mammals like bears hibernate',
        'They do!  It\'s just the nocturnal ones we interact with most that don\'t'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'They do!  It\'s just the nocturnal ones we interact with most that don\'t',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these things is UNTRUE about horses?',
      answers: [
        'Horses have the largest eyes of any land mammal',
        'A horses\' teeth take up more room in its head than its brain does',
        'Due to the physiology of a horse, they vomit at high speeds',
        'Horses can sleep while standing up or laying down'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Due to the physiology of a horse, they vomit at high speeds',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these things is UNTRUE about tortoises?',
      answers: [
        'They cannot feel through their shell',
        'A group of tortoises is called a creep',
        'They smell with their throat',
        'They reach sexual maturity with size, NOT age'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'They cannot feel through their shell',
    },
    {
      question: 'Do snakes have tails?',
      answers: [
      'No!  They have ribs throughout their body!',
      'Yes!  Their whole body is technically a tail!',
      'They used to, but they lost their tail when they lost their legs',
      'Yes they do!  It\'s the final portion of their body that\'s slightly thinner than the rest'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes they do!  It\'s the final portion of their body that\'s slightly thinner than the rest',
    },
    {
      question: 'Sharks tend to ____.',
      answers: [
        'Adapt extremely well to new environments',
        'Remember past injuries and plot revenge',
        'Attack anything and everything that comes within range',
        'Spend up to 50% of their day resting'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Adapt extremely well to new environments',
    },
    {
      question: 'As a California resident, which one of these bears should be most threatening to you?',
      answers: [
      'Grizzly bears!  They\'re our state animal for a reason!',
      'Brown bears!  They rival polar bears in size but live much closer to home!',
      'Black bears!  They\'re the only bears still IN California!',
      'Sun bears...?'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Black bears!  They\'re the only bears still IN California!',
    },
    {
      question: 'What type of animal would have been the biggest threat to our earlier ancestors? (and other primates still around today)',
      answers: [
        'Birds since they\'re so well adapted to prey on our young',
        'Snakes due to potent venom and extremely effective camouflage',
        'Canines since they are intelligent and adept pack hunters',
        'Felines due to their strength and stealth'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Felines due to their strength and stealth',
    }
];